Carlos Rossi

Motivated salesperson with 3+ years experience. Proven track record of meeting and exceeding sales goals in competitive environments. Relate well to diverse set of customers with strong skills in quickly determining needs and matching best product options to close deals.

Weston, FL carlos.rossi16@gmail.com (954) 515-8474

EXPERIENCE

Mypad, Sunrise, FL— Salesperson

MAY 2012 - APRIL 2014

Opened Store for business, developed strong communication and interpersonal skills, explained product offerings and, balanced cash registers at the end of shifts.

Charging on the Go, Sunrise, FL— Salesperson

JUNE 2014 - MAY 2015

Opened Store for business, practiced strong communication and interpersonal skills, explained product offerings and, balanced cash registers at the end of shifts.

GSM World Phones, Sunrise, FL— Salesperson

MAY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2015

Opened Store for business, practiced strong communication and interpersonal skills, explained product offerings and, balanced cash registers at the end of shifts.

EDUCATION

Broward College, Davie FL — AS Computer Programming

MAY 2015 - DECEMBER 2016

Application and web development, procedural and object-oriented programming and web design.

Broward College, Davie FL — BS Web Development

ONGOING

SKILLS

Goal driven.

People person.

Good listener.

Customer service mindset.

Conflict resolution.

Organization.

Eloquent speaker.

Mathematical aptitude.

Familiar with tech Products.

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent.

Spanish - Fluent.